
const statesAndCapitals = [
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Alabama", answer:["Montgomery"],digraph:["AL"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Alaska", answer:["Juneau"],digraph:["AS"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Arizona", answer:["Phoenix"],digraph:["AZ"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Arkansas", answer:["Little Rock"],digraph:["AK"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"California", answer:["Sacramento"],digraph:["CA"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Colorado", answer:["Denver"],digraph:["CO"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Connecticut", answer:["Hartford"],digraph:["CT"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Delaware", answer:["Dover"],digraph:["DE"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Florida", answer:["Tallahassee"],digraph:["FL"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Georgia", answer:["Atlanta"],digraph:["GA"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Hawaii", answer:["Honolulu"],digraph:["HI"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Idaho", answer:["Boise"],digraph:["ID"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Illinois", answer:["Springfield"],digraph:["IL"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Indiana", answer:["Indianapolis"],digraph:["IN"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Iowa", answer:["Des Moines"],digraph:["IA"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Kansas", answer:["Topeka"],digraph:["KS"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Kentucky", answer:["Frankfort"],digraph:["KY"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Louisiana", answer:["Baton Rouge"],digraph:["LA"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Maine", answer:["Augusta"],digraph:["ME"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Maryland", answer:["Annapolis"],digraph:["MD"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Massachusetts", answer:["Boston"],digraph:["MA"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Michigan", answer:["Lansing"],digraph:["MI"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Minnesota", answer:["Saint Paul"],digraph:["MN"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Mississippi", answer:["Jackson"],digraph:["MS"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Missouri", answer:["Jefferson City"],digraph:["MO"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Montana", answer:["Helena"],digraph:["MT"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Nebraska", answer:["Lincoln"],digraph:["NE"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Nevada", answer:["Carson City"],digraph:["NV"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"New Hampshire", answer:["Concord"],digraph:["NH"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"New Jersey", answer:["Trenton"],digraph:["NJ"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"New Mexico", answer:["Santa Fe"],digraph:["NM"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"New York", answer:["Albany"],digraph:["NY"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"North Carolina", answer:["Raleigh"],digraph:["NC"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"North Dakota", answer:["Bismarck"],digraph:["ND"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Ohio", answer:["Columbus"],digraph:["OH"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Oklahoma", answer:["Oklahoma City"],digraph:["OK"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Oregon", answer:["Salem"],digraph:["OR","OR"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Pennsylvania", answer:["Harrisburg"],digraph:["PA"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Rhode Island", answer:["Providence"],digraph:["RI"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"South Carolina", answer:["Columbia"],digraph:["SC"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"South Dakota", answer:["Pierre"],digraph:["SD"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Tennessee", answer:["Nashville"],digraph:["TN"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Texas", answer:["Austin"],digraph:["TX"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Utah", answer:["Salt Lake City"],digraph:["UT"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Vermont", answer:["Montpelier"],digraph:["VT"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Virginia", answer:["Richmond"],digraph:["VA"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Washington", answer:["Olympia"],digraph:["WA"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"West Virginia", answer:["Charleston"],digraph:["WV"]}, 
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Wisconsin", answer:["Madison"],digraph:["WI"]},
    { prefix:"state of ",question:"Wyoming", answer:["Cheyenne"],digraph:["WY"]}, 
];

exports.QsAndAs = statesAndCapitals;
